[
    {
        "id": 1,
        "front": "Test text 1",
        "back": "Test explanation 1",
        "box": 5
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "front": "Test text 2",
        "back": "Test explanation 2",
        "box": 4
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "front": "Test text 3",
        "back": "Test explanation 3",
        "box": 4
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "front": "Test text 4",
        "back": "Test explanation 4",
        "box": 2
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "front": "Test text 5",
        "back": "Test explanation 5",
        "box": 1
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "front": "Test text 6",
        "back": "Test explanation 6",
        "box": 1
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "front": "Test text 7",
        "back": "Test explanation 7",
        "box": 0
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "front": "Test text 8",
        "back": "Test explanation 8",
        "box": 0
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "front": "Test text 9",
        "back": "Test explanation 9",
        "box": 0
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "front": "Test text 10",
        "back": "Test explanation 10",
        "box": 0
    },
    {
        "id": 11,
        "front": "Test text 11",
        "back": "Test explanation 11",
        "box": 0
    },
    {
        "id": 12,
        "front": "Test text 12",
        "back": "Test explanation 12",
        "box": 0
    },
    {
        "id": 13,
        "front": "Test text 13",
        "back": "Test explanation 13",
        "box": 0
    },
    {
        "id": 14,
        "front": "Test text 14",
        "back": "Test explanation 14",
        "box": 0
    },
    {
        "id": 15,
        "front": "Test text 15",
        "back": "Test explanation 15",
        "box": 0
    },
    {
        "id": 16,
        "front": "Test text 16",
        "back": "Test explanation 16",
        "box": 0
    },
    {
        "id": 17,
        "front": "Test text 17",
        "back": "Test explanation 17",
        "box": 0
    },
    {
        "id": 18,
        "front": "Test text 18",
        "back": "Test explanation 18",
        "box": 6
    },
    {
        "id": 19,
        "front": "Test text 19",
        "back": "Test explanation 19",
        "box": 5
    },
    {
        "id": 20,
        "front": "Test text 20",
        "back": "Test explanation 20",
        "box": 4
    }
]